Thank you for watching!
Here you go! It's starting!
It's time for Hallo! This time we have Morning Musume。 23's Okamura Hamare,
Morning Musume。 23, and Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume。
This time, I'll be talking with the two of them, so please bear with me until the end.
This is Haruka's first time to be an MC for "Halo! Please introduce yourself.
She is a member of Morning Musume。 I am 17 years old, a sophomore in high school and a member of the 2317th term.
My special skill is calligraphy, and my hobby is collecting chocolate mint things.
The senior whom I admire is Homaru Okamura.
Thank you very much.
You said that I, Okamura, am the senior whom I admire,
By the way, I would like to ask you what you admire about him.
I am embarrassed.
I admire the gap between the performance of cool songs and cute songs,
I also like the funny parts.
Thank you very much.
I'm really sorry for making you say that,
Are you okay? He was talking about me, saying that my impression of you has changed,
I'm no longer the senior you admire?
No, I don't.
You don't? Is that so?
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. That's all I have to say,
Okamura, I am satisfied. Thank you very much.
And this October 25th is the release date of our new single, "Sukkousai Fever! Never Ending Shine!
So, I would like to briefly explain the three songs and tell you what you should listen to,
First of all, what do you think of "Wake Up Call" and "Never Ending Shine!
The song "Wake Up Call" is the first song that we, the members who have been without a band for 10 years, recorded in this single,
I sang the first part of the song, and we practiced it a lot, so I hope you will listen to it.
And "Sukkoku Fever! is really an amazing song, just like the title says. And Sukkoku Fever! is really an amazing song, just as the title suggests.
I think the point of the song is that it's pretty amazing,
The lyrics of the A-melody, B-melody, and chorus say very deep things, so I hope you will pay attention to them and listen to the song.
And Never Ending Shine!" is a song in which you can really enjoy Sei Fukumura's voice,
I would like you to listen to the song and pay attention to how the members draw each other with smiles on their faces.
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look at the video.
The result of the concert with all the members
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know everyone.
I made a mistake.
I made a mistake. I didn't know.
We all have bad faces.
Yes, I know. Today is the first day of the 17th term,
The 12th term,
12th term members,
It's in the family,
Thank you very much.
unforgettable memories,
Let's make unforgettable memories!
Let's work hard!
Please!
♪♪
That makeup doesn't suit you.
Forcing femininity on you that you can't wear
Unfortunately, it's not for you.
That's all I'm trying to say
Be pretty, be cool
Be cute, be cool, be cool, be cool azukutoku to kojo, love
A creature with no good nature
Any day must be fixed
It would surely be boring to leave it to others
I'll decide for myself, this feeling is unshakable
I don't want to deceive myself
Wake up! Goal!
It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
I love you
Just do it! Just do it!
Just do it
Just do it. Come on, now.
I'll light up someone's heart waiting for morning
Just let me, just let me, just let me, just let me
You can't see it when you're under full sail
You can't see it when you've lived it all
People have to be a little gentler
You can't find real service if you give up
Like a woman, like a man, too much resolution in your eyes
This voice is just a peek into my mai mai
A completely original girl
Sad, sad, sad, sad
Lovely, lovely, lovely
So much pain, so much suffering, so many contradictions
Such a creature, I've refused
I have to express it
Times are turning, towards happiness
It will never change. It will never change.
Everyone has colorful possibilities Colorful possibilities for everyone
It's time to wake up today
It's time to change myself It's time to be reborn, even if it's troublesome Just do it!
Someone's heart smoldering at the bottom of the night
I'll find it for you somewhere else
Touch baby touch baby touch baby touch baby
Hey, there's a lot of blurring Wake up call
Our Wake up call
Boring's not cool
Hey, that's up to you. Come here.
Ah wow
History made Foundation.
To childishly real Formation
Life's Motivation bathed in
Let's dance
Dance dance dance dance dance
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart
This music Just do it!
Something's waiting for the morning at the bottom of the night
Just me, I'll make you more
Dance baby!
The foundation that history creates
Join hands and weave out the formation
I'll open up the motivation of my life
Let's dance!
Dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance!
Hey angel, today is evolution
Smile and Genki, Revolution of LoveSmiles and Energy Revolution of Love
Ladies together Congrats!
Let's dance together!
Dance!
Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。 23's Haruka Inoue and the conductor Tako.
The performance at Line Cube Shibuya has just finished.
Yay!
This was the first time for us 17th term members to participate in the performance,
I was so nervous,
I was really nervous because I was nervous even when I went to bed,
But when I actually took the picture,
I was really nervous because I was so nervous even when I went to bed,
I was happy that I could see all the way up to the top.
I, Mieita, before the show,
I was not so nervous when I was in Japan,
I was so excited that I could do it,
But suddenly, right before the show, I got nervous,
Yamazaki-san patted me on the back,
Then Mr. Yamazaki patted me on the back, and Mr. Kitagawa said, "Goo, poof!
Goo, how do you call it?
Gutatch?
Gutatch? Gutatch,
Haga-san and Fukumura-san hugged me,
I was relieved.
Now, I'll tell them you did a great job.
Well then, se-no!
I will only have one first day as a new member, so I think this will probably be a wonderful memory for me, so please keep up the good work.
I was simply happy. I was happy because my sense of affirmation is very low,
I have very low self-esteem, so it's nice to hear that from someone else.
I have been working hard during the practice sessions, thinking that one day I will be able to enjoy it, or that one day someone will recognize me, I have been working hard during the practice sessions, thinking that one day I would be able to enjoy it, or that one day someone would recognize me for it,
I am still a girl, but to be told for the first time that I did my best, and to have it said by the person who was the hardest to beat, I was so happy that I couldn't help but start to cry.
I think that today's speech was my very first one, so I would like to keep that in mind and do my best from now until the last arena in Yokohama.
So, I will continue to do my best!
Are you having fun? Please watch the rest of the show!
Morning Musume。 23's Ahomare Okamura and Haruka Inoue will be presenting the "Halo! STE!
From here, I'd like to talk a little about each other. I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
Yes, I will do my best.
Okay, here we go.
What do you cherish most in a day?
Time to eat.
In reference to your new song "Sukkoku Sukkoku Fever," when is the moment when Haruka-chan gets "Sukkoku Sukkoku Fever"?
When the light is green.
I want to achieve it as Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。 What do you want to accomplish as Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。
To show my charm as a Kansai person.
How do you like your steak cooked?
I like it well cooked.
This year marks the 25th anniversary of Hello Project. Which song would you like to sing someday?
The Osaka love song by Morning Musume。 s Osaka Koi no Uta (Osaka Love Song).
Thank you very much.
There were quite a few items that caught my attention.
In reference to the "Super Fever," the question was, "When is the moment you get feverish?
When the light is green.
Does that mean the moment when you can cross a few green lights?
Yes, when the light turns green at the right time. When the light turns green at the right time.
I know.
When you are walking and you see a traffic light,
It's a great feeling when you see a traffic light and think it's going to turn red and it turns green, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Also, I was asked which song I would like to sing someday on the 25th anniversary of Hello Project. I was asked which song I would like to sing someday on the 25th anniversary of Hello Project, Also, which song would you like to sing someday on the 25th anniversary of Hello Project? I was asked which song I would like to sing someday on the 25th anniversary of Hello Project,
Osaka love song.
I would like to hear it.
I'm the only Kansai person among the current members,
Of course. I'm the only one.
I'd like to sing it because the lyrics include "I love you.
I like the real Osaka. I don't mean "I love you.
I would love to hear a love song.
Questions for Mr. Okamura will come after the VTR.
Hallo! Ste.
Amazing, amazing, amazing, amazing.
Only this one lie will end it all.
Morning Musume。' 23 Suptoku kudoku fever!
Now on sale!
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
Taiyo ha tomokoto
Morning Musume。 23 Wake up call
Now on sale!
If I have to say it, human being is just a stupid girl
Morning Musume。 23 featuring Mizuki Fukumura
Never ending shine
Now on sale!
Halo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Okamura-san some questions!
I'll do my best!
You opened an Instagram account this June.
What has changed since you started SNS?
I go to a café that looks good on SNS on my days off.
New song "Wake up call New song Wake up call Why do you wake up when you wake up?
What do you always do to wake up in the morning?
I drink a quantity of lactobacilli that improves the quality of sleep.
Okamura-san is known for his meat.
What is the most shocking meat you have encountered recently?
A very large teabowl steak.
It was delicious!
The number of junior members is increasing.
What is your role in Morning Musume。 If you had to sum up your role in the group, how would you describe it?
I tell them before my seniors do.
What costume would you like to wear for Halloween this year?
Very girly!
Yes!
And that's the end of my answer.
Is there anything that caught your attention?
Yes, so what costume would you like to try for Halloween this year?
Yes, I'd like to dress up like a Heisei gal.
I wonder if you can call it this year.
It's kind of a boom.
Loose socks and the like are all the rage.
You know, the batch, the dipped socks...
Three, four, five layers of socks.
And makeup.
I really wanted to do it right.
Yes, I do.
I want to do it.
I'd like to do it, if I have a chance to do it.
I would like to do it.
If you had to sum up your role in the current Morning Musume。 If you had to sum up your role in Morning Musume。
To tell the story before my seniors. Tell them before your seniors
I thought this question was pretty hard to answer.
I thought it would be more difficult if the junior staff had a diary under them and the senior staff had a diary under them.
The youngest is Rio Sakurai, who is a member of the 16th term
Rio Sakurai, a member of the 16th term
I want them to watch Rio Sakurai's back first and foremost.
I think that's what my seniors say.
I think that's what she said to me.
And, I don't know...
The most senior members.
9th term, 10th term...
Well, they are all seniors to me.
I have to warn my seniors.
I tell them before they tell their seniors.
I try not to let my seniors
I hope I can make them not to say such a thing.
I think it would be good if I could do that.
I'm not very good at communicating.
I'm not good at communicating, so I'd like to learn from that.
I hope we can learn from each other and be more careful with each other.
Harustei will continue after this.
This is Masashi Natsuyaki.
I'm Sakura Oda from Morning Musume。 I am Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。
I will continue to do my best to make delicious food.
What would you like to make this time?
I would like to make chawanmushi (steamed egg custard).
And I will make stuffed peppers and meat stuffing.
So you are going to make two things this time,
Yes.
Let's see....What a surprise!
Wow, it's so beautiful.
It smells so good.
This time, I would like to make stuffed peppers.
Okay.
Well then, let's start with what we're going to do.
Yes, sir. First of all, chop the onion a little.
Yes, you can do that. You can do it.
You really don't need that much.
This time, 30 grams.
I want to make it bigger.
How can I make it less painful?
Is there something wrong with it?
It's just a little bit too much.
Oh, really?
I've crushed the fibers.
The smell.
Yes, it does. It comes out.
If you don't feel it with your hand like this, you won't cry?
If you hold your nose.
Well, I used to do that a lot.
Goggles.
Yes, yes.
Does that have anything to do with it? After all.
No, I guess it just comes in.
But I guess it comes in through the nose.
But if you just cut it off quickly.
Quickly.
Speedy, yes. That's important.Speedy, yes. That's important.
Put it in a plastic bag.
Yes.
When I make hamburgers, I often say, "Make the chopped onions rain-colored.
That's a lot of work.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's orange.
So, I put these onions in a bag and lightly inflate the bag.
Fold them up like this without tying them up.
Then, the steam escapes a little bit.
But it still accumulates.
Fluff it up.
Fluffy.
Microwave for about 1 minute.
In the meantime, split the peppers in half.
Like this.
It's better to make it into a bowl.
It depends on the shape of the bell pepper.
Yes, yes.
I think the larger the surface area, the better.
And then, put this seed in the pepper.
By hand.
Yes, by hand.
With the caps.
Do you mean here with the seeds?
You can take it with the bako.
Oh.
And the onions are already done in a minute.And the onions are already in this in a minute.
Oh, shinashi shinashi.
They're translucent.
That's enough.
And this is hot.
Put them in the freezer.
Freezer.
Put it in the freezer for about 5 minutes.
So you can put it in the freezer like this?
Yes, it's fine.
This is where the real fun begins.
You're still using plastic bags,
Put all the ground meat in here.
Then, rub it well.
By this salt rubbing, the proteins are bound together and become sticky,
The proteins are bound together and become sticky,
It's like a bonding process.
And when it is well done, crack an egg into the mixture,
Crack an egg and put it in,
It's so easy!
Mash the egg a little bit,
Then mix it in.
Amazing!
If you use minced chicken meat, you can make a little more.
Indeed! This is so versatile.
You can also make pasta and meatball pasta.
Amazing!
Then tie it up,
It depends on the type of plastic bag, It depends on the type of this plastic bag,
Put the tip in.
Wow!
And..,
A squeeze bag!
Careful, careful.
Okay, can I just leave it like that?
Okay.
Wow!
And flatten it out a bit.
Okay.
Wow! Looks good!
Looks good!
Looks delicious! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Let's grill it!
I put a thin layer of oil on the meat, but since it's a double-boiler, a good amount of oil comes out of the meat, so I think it should be fine,
If it sticks a little, I'll add a little more oil.
If it sticks to the meat, I would add a little more oil.
If you add oil at the beginning, it will be difficult to get the meat to brown if it is covered with oil, so less oil is better.
Yes.
If you use tongs, sometimes the meat sticks to the pan.
If you use a spatula like this, it would be better to use a spatula and cook it quickly.
Wow! Looks delicious!
And then put the lid back on, like we're waiting here again.
Let's wait.
Normally, it only takes a couple of minutes.
Yeah. The peppers are fast, aren't they?
It's fast.
The peppers themselves are not that big, so the minced meat is rather thin.The peppers themselves are not that big, so the ground meat is relatively thin.
If you cook the meat side well, you can get about 70% of it in.
Wow.
Wow! Looks good!
Wow! The juices from the meat are amazing.
This one is good, too. Press it lightly.
It's firm.
Yes, it is. And here, I have an important announcement.
Yes. Wait a minute. There it is.
Early point!
There it is.
Don't spill the juice from the peppers.
It's already spilling out.
It's already overflowing.
Aaah! Watch out!
Wow! The juices are flowing!
This is a little... I'll just soak up the excess oil.
Is this excess?
Extra oil.
It's also gravy, but there's a lot of oil.
This is where the teacher loves to start the fire.
Fire!
It's a bit jumpy.
Here we go.
Wow!
Cool!
Put it on fire, and when it's cooked down, have the fire turn off once.
A little bit, this is already about.
It's still a little loose in there.
If you cook it down a little slower, it will turn into a hamburger sauce. If you boil it down a little slowly, it becomes like hamburger sauce.
Smells great!
Here it is.
When transferring to a plate, as usual, be careful not to let the juices drip down.
Yes, be careful.
Not too hot?
This one spills more.
No, it looks delicious!
Yes, beautiful!
I think it's good!
It's done!
Chawanmushi and stuffed peppers are ready!
Now, what do you think? How do you like it, Sakura?
Doesn't it look really good?
The stuffed peppers are cute and heart-shaped,
And the steamed egg custard is also very beautiful,
The chawanmushi is also very beautifully hardened, and it's already very firm.
Please try it right away.
I'll try it now.
What do you think?
It's perfect. It's so beautiful!
Amazing! It's not even close! Just like the ones you see in the store!
Bon appétit!
I'm so happy! Delicious!
The way it hardens is perfect.
It's because I usually make it without ingredients,
I usually make it without ingredients, but when I add crab or shrimp, the flavor comes out in the bullet liquid,
I can taste the flavor of the bullet liquid.
You can taste that and it is so delicious.
And I also made stuffed peas this time,And since I also made the stuffed peas this time,
We will eat it.
I'm going to eat it.
Delicious.
If you want to conquer green peppers, you should eat the stuffed peppers first.
I definitely think so.
It's delicious.
It was good.
I'm glad.
It was delicious. Both the chawanmushi and the stuffed peppers were great.
Was it a good experience for you?
It was good.
I now have more dishes in my repertoire,
I was surprised at how easy it was to make the stuffed bell peppers.
It's true.
But it's so easy to make.
I can make it today.
I can do it. I bought green peppers on the way home.
I was very satisfied with the successful appearance of Hello!
I was very satisfied.
I hope you will come to Hello!
I hope you will come to our Hello! I look forward to seeing you again.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now, Hello!
Bye bye.
I'm so hungry. I'm so hungry.
I thought it would be delicious just to cook and drink.
Have you done any cooking lately, Haruka? Haruka, have you done any cooking lately?
Yes, I have. I don't cook much, but I often eat natto.
I don't cook at all, just fry an egg or sausage, but I love natto.
Do you eat natto as a regular bowl of rice?
Yes, I do. I eat it on rice.
Do you have any other condiments you like?
I eat kimchi and eggs together.
I don't really care about the kimchi, but it depends on whether I put only the yolk or the white of the egg.
All eggs.
All of them?
Yes, all of them.
Do you mix them? Well.
I mix them.
I see. So that's how it is.
I am also very particular about natto. I really like natto, but there is a sauce called mellow kelp dashi that I really love. That's all I eat.
My parents don't have any natto, so I ask them to buy me some mellow kelp dashi for sure.
Natto is great. It's really very versatile.
It goes well with ramen, udon, pasta, and rice.
Isn't it amazing?
That's why I like it so much. Natto is so versatile.
Just mixing natto and making a bowl of rice is a great dish, you know.
Thank you for watching.
Well then, let's go for it in earnest!
I love you.
Dom, katakana conquered!
This love was never a mistake
I won't cry
If you want it, you'll get it
I can't cry
When I met you I met you.
The wish I made on this day
What was the love I had before this?
The future I was embracing
Canfor! On! Dee! Hi!
Smile Pantree!
It's our dream to perform overseas.
What? What?
That's amazing! Is it like that?
Thank you so much for coming!
Thank you very much!
Free rum. More stars than stars.
Love, love, love, if that's all there is
Freelum, get strong, get started
I'm so sleepy I could fall asleep
One more time, in my dreams, I'll fly away
Good night
[ED]
I'm off!
Good morning.
I'm off. I'll do my best.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Over there. That way.
I'm going.
See you at Soumonie Live.
Bye bye.
I'm off.
Please don't give up.
Just still emotion by emotion. Just yet, feelings and all
I want to be held by you
I just can't take that first step
I can't take that step
If you break it
Today I'm in Taiwan
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Now, on behalf of beautiful Nikko, I invite you to Marin.
Hello everyone.
I am looking forward to today's concert.
Please enjoy it with all of you.
Run-run-run-run-run-run-run.
Time History
Previous First But anything is okay
Each with love
We're going to make it happen.
You hate it, don't you?
When it's gone.
I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll do it.
And that's okay.
I'm proud of you. Ride it out today.
I'll be right here in front of you
WOOO YOU MAKE ME FEEL SO GOOD
that make me feel so good
so i love love love love
Thank you, Subakyan-chan.
Seino, this is Tsubaki Factory.
Tsubaki Factory's performance in Hong Kong and Taiwan has ended. Tsubaki Factory's Hong Kong and Taiwan tour has ended.
Yay!
It was fun.
It was so much fun.
How was it? How was it, everyone?
I felt the audience's reaction was bigger than usual,
It was amazing.
I felt like I was 14 years old in love,
The first four people joined in,
And the reactions were always the same every time.
Yay!
Yay! I was so happy to see that.
That made me very happy.
I was a little embarrassed.
I was embarrassed.
It was different,
There were Kanto and Chinese,
We were trying to learn and speak as much as possible,
But everyone learned a lot of Japanese,
But everyone learned a lot of Japanese, and they understood the language very well even without an interpreter,
I was very happy to see that they could understand us without an interpreter,
It made me very happy,
I also felt that I would like to be able to speak more in the local language.
Thank you very much.
I learned a lot.
A lot.
Really.
There was the story-telling session, the postcard handover session, and the photo session,
And there was also a photo session, right?Also, there was a photo session, wasn't there?
So, both local people and those who came from Japan,
I was very happy to be able to be involved with them,
I was very happy to be able to be involved with both the local people and those who came from Japan,
I was also happy to be able to say thank you to each and every one of them,
I was able to express my gratitude to each and every one of them, and to say "J.J.J., the light bulb",
I was very happy to be able to express my gratitude to each and every one of them,
I was very happy to be able to express my gratitude to each one of them.
It was very precious.
But...,
How was it?
It was a personal thing for me,
I did some stirring in the local language,
I'm glad.
The local people understood me a little,
I was happy that the local people understood me and said "yay" to me.
I think it was a priority.
I was happy.
I was very happy to see so many smiling faces of the fans.
Also.
Tsubaki, I hope you have some college support or something.
Best regards.
That's all for now.
That was Tsubaki and Mie.
Thank you very much.
I am Shun Okamura of Morning Musume。 I am Shun Okamura from Morning Musume。
Haruka Inoue is presenting Halo! STE.
I would like to dig a little deeper to let you know more about Haruka-chan.
I've asked her manager about episodes in her life. I would like to introduce some of the episodes that I heard from her manager. I asked the manager what kind of person Haruka Inoue is. I would like to introduce some of the episodes that I heard from the manager.
What I thought Haruka Inoue was cute
Inoue speaks in Kansai dialect to staff members who are from Kansai, but the other day she said, "I'm not..." It was very cute. It was very cute. I have never heard of it.
I have never heard of it. I have Kansai dialect. Kansai dialect? I knew it.
Yes, I do. Yes, I do. It comes out when I talk with people from Kansai.
I see.
You mean you feel the same nuance?
Yes, that's right.
I see.
It doesn't come out when you are talking with me?
I don't think it comes out much when I am with my senpai.
Do you think honorifics and the Kansai dialect are different?
Yes, I do. I think it is difficult to mix them.
I see. So, I guess I would like to hear a little bit about the Kansai dialect. I would like to hear a little bit about the Kansai dialect.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Haruka-chan's cute Kansai dialect.
Three, two, one.
I love it!
So cute!
Thank you for the food. I got it for liking it.
So, now I would like to tell you about my own episode.
My impression of Haruka-chan is that she is calm and everyone loves her,
I don't think she realizes it, but I have the impression that during dance practice, the more she concentrates, the more her mouth opens.
Do you notice this yourself?
I don't know if I had noticed it, but I noticed it when my manager told me the other day that Inoue's mouth was open.
I see.
Do you open your mouth when you are thinking or concentrating?
Yes, I do. That's right.
I didn't know that.I didn't know.
You didn't know.
But I also noticed that after I joined the company, I say a lot of things, and when I talk, I tend to manual-write a lot.
But I think it's cute, so I don't think you have to stop,
But I think you should consider whether to open your mouth or close it depending on the place and use it accordingly.
Shall I say hello again?
Yes.
Shall we go in Kansai dialect, Hagoromo?
Yes, I would like to go.
I would like to go.
I look forward to working with you.
There are still many things I'm not good at, but I'll keep working hard, so please support me.
She's cute. Perfect.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to burn out. Just this love.
Whatever the endgame, I'm prepared for it.
I can barely afford it.
I'm just clinging on for dear life.
Hey, sweet, gossipy arms
♪ Everything, everything, everything ♪ It's the first time we've ever been together
Kiss me, don't let go
Kiss me, don't let it be so natural
Wipe away this insecurity
Hey, I'm here
With your fingertips, with your eyes
Wrap me in your arms
Believe Believe
I love you
Kiss me Dangerously Kiss me Dangerously
Kiss me Sweet kisses
Make all these wishes come true
With my soul
In this moment
Gently reassure me
Please Please
I love you
Please Please Please
Let's do our best tomorrow!
Morning Musume。 13's Hamari Akumura and Haruka Inoue will be presenting "Halo! STE, presented by Hamari Akamura and Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume'13.
It's time to say goodbye.
Yes, this is Haruka's first time to be an MC for Hallo! How was the recording?
Yes, I was very nervous because it was my first time to be an MC,
It was a fun time and I got to know a lot about Akamura-san.
I also had a lot of fun with Haruka-chan,
I never thought I would be chosen as the first MC with a new member,
I also felt that I had become a bit of a senior.
Yes, it was a great recording. Thank you very much.
So I have an announcement.
Today, on the day of distribution, the new single "Sukkousoku Fever!
Ever Ending Shine has been released.
All three songs are very suitable for the current Morning Musume。 I think all three songs are perfect for the current Morning Musume,
This is the first single for the 17th term members,
And for Sei Fukumura, it is her last single,
It is the first single for the 17th term members and the last single for Sei Fukumura.
I hope everyone will listen to it.I hope everyone will listen to it a lot.
Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn Ever Ending Shine show is underway.
The next shows will be in Yokohama on November 3 and Nagoya Park on November 4. This is Mizuki Fukumura's last tour and the first tour for the 17th term members.
It is the first tour for the 17th term members. We will do our best to improve our skills and run through to the end.
On November 28, we will hold the "Never Ending Employee Award Special" and on November 29, we will hold the "Never Ending Employee Award Sanctuary: Mizuki Fukumura Graduation Special" at Yokohama Arena.
I was really surprised to hear that we will be performing two days at Yokohama Arena. I am quite nervous now, but there were many wonderful guests for the special event.
I was really surprised to hear that the concert will be held at Yokohama Arena on two days, and I am quite nervous now.
I was not able to attend the 25th anniversary concert.
I was not able to attend the 25th anniversary concert, so I am very happy that I will be able to take revenge there.
I am very happy. I will do my best.
Also, Morning Musume。's 23 and Anjum will appear on Countdown Japan 2324 on December 29. 23 and Anjelum will be performing at the Countdown Japan 2324 on December 29.
This will be the first time for me and the 17th term members to attend Countdown Japan, so I'm a bit nervous, but I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it. Project members will appear more and more on the channel.
Project members. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
Please subscribe to the channel. 23's Motoon Ogura and Haruka Inoue,
Haruka Inoue.
Farewell!